Pip?
You ready?
How much?
Which one? Which one?
Sawahdee kah!
Kabayan!
- Filipino?
- Yes!
Kabayan!
Bro, help me out,
you know where this is?
What's the address?
It's my employer, man.
Yeah, I know where that is!
- I'll bring you there.
- Really?
- Come on!
- Seriously?
Yeah, I know it!
Come on.
Thanks, man.
It's good there's a lot of Pinoys
here in Thailand.
Yeah, of course I'll help you.
Appreciate it.
- Kabayan, are we there yet?
- Almost there!
Get all his stuff!
Check his bag!
Hey! Let me go!
Hold him!
There's a Buddhist saying that goes...
"If you meet Buddha on the road,
kill him."
It's probably an illusion.
Me?
I've already seen the most
beautiful illusion.
Hey!
Careful.
We're almost there.
Just a sec.
Come in.
Thank you.
Ouch!
Stay there.
I'm going to get medicine for you.
Don't look, alright?
You aren't a pervert,
are you?
No way.
I know you're Filipino,
even if you don't look like one.
Let me do that.
You're like a kid.
Go! I told you to go!
- Don't come here!
- You don't want me anymore?
I don't want you anymore!
- You might regret this.
- Go! Leave me alone!
We broke up!
No!
- I like you.
- I don't like you!
Go!
What the fuck,
go away!
Or I will call the police!
Call them,
so they can deport you!
Is this your new guy?
- Leave us alone!
- You asshole!
Go! Just go!
Stop coming and seeing me!
Go!
Shithead!
Who was that?
My ex. Let's talk inside.
Sorry about that.
So who was it?
My ex.
He owns the bar in Patpong
I used to work at
during my early days in Thailand.
Where do you work now?
Secret.
I came to Thailand
to become a teacher.
But I wasn't so lucky.
That's why I ended up
in Cake's bar.
Cake?
What kind of name
is Cake?
Is that a call sign?
He's a thug,
but his name is Cake.
You moron, it's not like that.
That's just his nickname.
His real name is Ittipong.
- That's just how it is in Thailand.
- Ittipong.
His sibling's name is Donut.
- The fuck?
- Why are you laughing?
If you know what they're like,
you wouldn't be laughing!
- It's a stupid name.
- He has a lot of connections
that's why he can threaten
to have me deported.
What does he really want?
He wants us to get back together,
and go work at his bar again.
But he also wants me
to accept that
he's going to have
other girls, too.
I don't want that!
Not even for your peace of mind?
No thanks!
Wanna go back to
the Philippines, then?
I do, but...
Do I want my siblings to starve?
No way.
Look here,
I bought a cellphone
for my sibling.
Because he wanted
to do Tik-Tok.
It's cute, right?
You?
What will you do now?
Find my employer.
Do you remember the address?
Don't worry.
I'll help you.
Over here.
Here.
I wrote the directions there, okay?
You shouldn't get lost.
I don't get why you're doing this,
but thanks.
Especially for the phone.
You moron, it's nothing!
We'll help each other.
Same country and all.
You keep that for now,
but give it back
because I still need to send that
home to my sibling.
Yes, boss.
Thanks a lot!
You need to walk two blocks,
keep going straight.
When you get to the white building,
take a tuk-tuk.
Then get down and your office
should be there.
No!
We don't have issue this!
We are not looking for employees.
Ma'am,
my agency gave this to me,
this paper.
No, I don't have job.
No agency.
- Okay?
- Ma'am,
- Okay, okay.
- can you give me any job?
Ma'am, please, I'm begging,
I have no one else!
So, how'd it go?
Bad.
It was a scam.
The agency doesn't even exist.
Huh? I don't get it.
They gave me fake documents.
I didn't find work.
Nevermind.
There's loads of work here.
You just need to lay low for now.
I'll ask around the Pinoy Community.
Don't worry.
Let's walk around.
I know how you feel!
I've been there.
When I didn't get a job as a teacher,
I just thought...
What's gonna happen
to my six siblings now?
They already gave me a list
before I even left.
They all wanted shoes.
Like, fuck! What now?
I hooked up with Cake.
I didn't know he had other girls.
And now that I want out,
he's trying to get me back.
I just want to go back to the Philippines.
You sure?
I can help you get
work here, you know.
Probably not in Bangkok, though.
Maybe in the provinces.
At least you'll earn something.
Whatever gets you by, that's it?
Exactly!
I just realized
I've never made a selfish decision.
Everything had to include
my family.
Right? That's why we're
going to have fun now.
But I'm broke!
Did I make you pay
for anything?
It's my treat, so let's go!
I made Cake my boyfriend
so I could keep my job.
You want to just buy clothes?
Or you're sticking to that?
Ow!
Hey, you've got a good eye!
Really?
Yeah!
See? Looks good.
You wanna go here?
No, not here!
- Why?
- I might run into Cake's men.
So what? We're just going
to drink.
Forget it, let's go!
You know, I used to be a bar girl.
That was my first job.
But I'm a college graduate,
mind you!
Really?
You're kind of nosy.
Aren't we buddies?
You took me around town for free.
Shut up and drink.
- Cheers!
Is that a kiss mark?
Did I do that?
That's a birthmark.
Unique, right?
If I die, I'll be identified immediately.
Why are you so morbid?
We're really talking
about that after sex?
- What topic did you have in mind?
- Anything!
You haven't even told me
where you live!
In Albay.
Albay?
There's a small village there,
where, if you ask anybody,
they know immediately
where Jessy lives.
What about you?
Where do you live?
Isabela.
But I went to highschool in Manila.
With my uncle.
Can I hug you?
Would I refuse now?
Come here.
Here's your fare.
Take care at work, okay?
And don't let go of this.
Most of all, don't let them know you're...
- you know.
- What?
Illegal?
I'm not illegal!
Who are you talking about?
Don't be loud.
But, really, thanks.
If it weren't for you,
I'd never get a job,
I'd probably be back home empty-handed.
Don't mention it.
You know...
I want to visit you
on my days off.
No matter how far,
I'll be there.
You don't need to!
I actually want to do video calls with you.
I charge extra for video calls.
Really?
I'm kidding!
No, really, how much?
I'm kidding, you idiot!
You're too serious!
Line up there!
I need to give you something.
- Oh! You don't need it anymore?
- Nope.
- Got a new one.
- Wow!
Give me that.
Don't really want to see Hello Kitty
while masturbating.
This is it.
Take care.
You, too.
See you around.
Do you know this address?
- Ah, here!
- Here?
- Yes. Thank you.
- Thank you.
- Jessy! How are you?
- I'm good.
I just finished working.
- How are you?
- I'm okay.
I get three square meals a day.
They pay me some
so it's fine.
By the way,
I'll visit you next weekend!
Up to you. I'm always here for you.
Take care.
I'll visit on my day off.
I miss you.
Sure thing. I'm always here.
I'm here.
Show me.
There.
Move closer.
Put your hand in.
Where? Down there?
Lower.
Lower, lower.
Keep going.
Busy?
The subscriber cannot be reached.
Please try again later.
Yes?
You're looking for Jessy?
Yes! Do you know where she is?
Ah, some guys from
immigration took her.
Immigration?
My friend, one more.
Jessy.
What the fuck?
Fuck you, Cake.
Thanks, mister.
Uncle Gani?
What is it?
Uncle,
it's Pip!
Oh!
- Motherfucker!
- How are you?
Wait a sec!
Pip!
What happened to you?
Oh, wait, wait.
Well?
You didn't even say you were coming?
Come in, come in.
Do your parents even know you're back?
I gotta earn money here in Manila first.
What, you think no one will recognize you?
Manila is so small!
Doesn't matter.
Wait a minute.
Why did you think
to come here?
Well.
You're my asshole of an uncle!
Oh!
Sorry, sorry. Uncle.
Fine, you can stay here.
But don't give me a headache.
I won't.
Your folks might think I'm
letting you get away with shit!
Uncle! What's that?
Wait, that's mine.
So what is it?
Betting App.
Betting?
Yeah!
You've never heard of it?
Online gambling.
There's a lot of games here.
You have Cara Y Cruz.
There's color game,
Tong-its.
Oh, it's like... online cockfighting.
They have that, too.
Does it pay a lot, uncle?
Pay? This is gambling!
You'll only know how much you get
once you play.
How do you get the money?
E-cash.
Online banking.
Hey Pip.
Don't even think about it.
You're broke enough as it is.
What's this
"Knock-Out" at Pataya?
I can't get in.
I haven't tried that yet.
I think you need 100 thousand pesos
credits to get in.
Look at those girls there,
the ones manning the rooms.
This is just a rumor I heard...
Those girls go naked
and give live shows!
But you need
to have 100 thousand pesos.
I don't have that kind of money.
And if I did, why would I
waste it on beat-ups and boobs?
High, please! High, high!
Shit!
Finally, I'm winning!
Jessy?
Wait, I'm confused.
So you're saying that you came here,
right here at the precinct,
to look for a missing woman,
who isn't actually missing
because you saw her?
Kind of, yeah.
You're saying she was kidnapped?
She wasn't kidnapped.
I told you, I just saw her.
Hang on, did you try
all her social media accounts?
What about her number? Just text her.
I've done all that.
It's either deactivated,
or just keeps ringing.
Maybe you got ghosted.
You know, boy.
I don't think you need our help.
You'll have better luck
pitching to Jessica Soho.
Send your story to their show.
We're busy with actual crimes here.
Just last night,
a father stabbed their kid.
An addict and a drunkard.
We're not going to
prioritize you over that, sonny.
Got it, sir. Thanks anyway.
Wait.
You said you saw this woman again, right?
Where?
Let's hit up DSWD or something.
I feel bad for you.
Don't pity me.
Come on!
Just tell me where you saw her.
Online.
I thought you said you already
hit up her socials?
Online gambling.
She ferries players.
How can you tell it's her?
I know something about her.
Alright. Let's dig into this.
Online gambling, huh?
From what we know,
that compound is where
their operations are.
You know someone from the inside?
We've had complaints but,
we don't have any evidence.
And their business is registered,
so we can't do anything.
Just don't let them know
you got their address from us.
Good day.
What is it?
Hello. I wanted to apply for
an IT position for the Pataya App.
They said this was
the application center?
Someone referred me here,
maybe you know them.
Here.
Aiko!
What?
Why are you showing us
someone's boobs?
You think we know
each other's boobs here?
No, I mean--
Wait! I know her!
Really?
Wait! Kate! Kate!
Girl with a birthmark
on her boob, this guy's asking.
Me? Are you looking for me?
Sorry.
I didn't mean to...
stare.
My cellphone.
Alright, you guys go upstairs.
Okay, so now that you've
seen me, what do you want?
Sorry. I was just looking for a woman
with a birthmark on her chest.
It looks like a heart, like yours.
When I saw you on the app,
I thought I found her.
And now you know that it's not me,
why are you still here?
Well, I saw you and thought...
maybe we could be friends.
Wow, that's some pick-up line.
How many girls have you used it on?
It's not a pick-up line.
I'm just being honest.
Here.
Oh shit, it's real.
But that's not me.
Is she your girlfriend?
Well, our birthmarks are different.
Hers is shaped like a heart.
Mine is...
shaped like a dong.
Hey, I'm proud of it!
It doesn't grow when you caress it, though.
I'm Kate.
Pip.
Ah, Kate!
Could I have your number?
I'm not easy to get, but...
if...
you're really interested,
you can visit later.
You already know where we live.
Shit.
Pip, you fucking moron!
Lock your damn door!
Pervert!
Goddamn it!
- Uncle!
- Let's eat.
Sorry about last night.
Can we not talk about that shit?
I might lose my appetite.
Sorry, uncle.
How's the job hunt going?
It's going.
Oh, your mom called.
She's asking for money.
Said she'll pay me back
when you've sent them some.
Alright, I'll take care of it.
Go find some work first you dumbass,
so you can actually send something.
Stop jacking off!
Hi!
What are you here for?
I'm waiting for Kate.
Are you her boyfriend?
No, just a friend.
Fubu?
What's Fubu?
Nevermind.
Do you know who I am?
Has Kate told you about me?
No.
Are you one of the other girls?
Me?
I know we're close in age,
but,
I assure you,
we work in different departments.
Sorry, ma'am, but who are you?
Nina.
I'm one of the operators here.
I take care of the girls.
So tell me. What do you want from Kate?
I just want to be friends.
Don't take me for a fool, boy.
I know that leads to fucking in the end!
I don't have a problem with that.
But,
what work do you do?
Don't tell me my girl
has to feed you, too?
Honestly, I'm still looking for work.
I'm supposed to be in Thailand. OFW.
But I got scammed.
What can you do?
Plenty.
Call me if you can't find anything.
Maybe I'll have something for you.
Thanks.
Take care, you two.
I guess you've met my boss!
Don't get knocked up, okay?
I'll go now.
Whoever you're thinking of,
I'm the one here now.
Pip.
Wake up.
We still have work.
Huh? Work? What time?
It's nine o'clock.
I guess you had fun last night!
Kate.
What is it?
Sorry.
For what?
For last night.
I was hammered last night.
I don't really have sex with others.
Okay... why are you explaining this?
I want it to be... just us.
I don't want you to
think differently of me.
That's alright.
I mean, just because
you have sex with others
doesn't mean you love them, right?
But I'm only after you.
You know what, I'll tell you.
If we do end up being a thing,
I'm cool if you have sex with others.
I know the girls here
will take care of you.
And I know the girls who
will have sex with you anyway.
- Right, ladies?
- Of course.
Are you serious?
Do I look like I'm kidding?
I don't know.
I've never met anyone like you.
Get used to it.
Go on, I have work to do.
There's your kid.
You piece of shit!
Sixta, that's enough!
Pip!
You think you can lie to me?
I thought you were in Thailand!
Where did you come from?
Did you actually go to Thailand?
The agency was fake.
There was nothing for me there.
When did you come home?
Are you trying to make fools out of us?
No.
I'm really not, mom.
Then you should have just come home!
Why didn't you tell me anything?
I don't know what
you're doing with your life
and with ours!
I thought you said
you were going to help?
But here you are wasting your life away,
like you don't have a family!
Your father is old!
Mom.
Don't worry.
I found work.
What is it?
Look at you. All that bravado.
Now you're begging.
What do you have for me?
Do you think you get to choose?
I thought you said
you had plenty of talents,
and you're up for anything?
I don't know if I can do sex work.
Why would you think that?
It's getting late.
Well. Everyone who works
sells their body in a way.
Chefs get wounded.
Call center agents develop
hypertension from stress.
You can't get anywhere
without selling your body.
So what is it then?
Am I gonna be a call boy?
No.
Then what?
No more questions.
Where are we going?
Are you deaf?
Didn't I say no more questions?
You'll have to excuse me,
I've had bad experiences on narrow alleys.
Welcome to your new office.
What is this?
This is Patayan (To the Death).
I don't like this shit.
I thought you could do lots of things?
But I'm not a boxer.
You just need to fight.
Haven't you gotten into fistfghts
when you were younger?
Sorry, Nina, I can't do this.
Even if I tell you 80 thousand is the
lowest you can get when you lose?
Obviously, it's bigger if you win.
There's no age limit,
no weight divisions. Just fight.
But how do you earn from this?
You see this?
This match right now
has a total bet of eight million.
And that isn't a big fight.
It's just like online cockfighting,
but with people.
But unlike cockfighting,
here, entertainment is important.
The audience wants blood and broken bones.
No gloves, no safety.
Our audience are businessmen. Politicians.
They're sick and tired of their safe lives.
Every now and then,
to release their animal instinct,
they want to participate
in something risky.
Violence.
Stuff they can't experience
from their penthouse condominiums.
We had one boxer
who got so beat up,
he ended up with a
hole in his lungs. Dead.
But because the fight was good,
one of our high betters took pity on him.
They added an extra 50 thousand
as an offering to the family.
Not a bad deal.
"Not a bad deal"? These are
people's lives on the line.
If he were alive, where would
he get 50 thousand?
I'm pretty sure he'd rather die for it.
Thank you.
Take care, you two.
Hey, why didn't you say
you were with Miss Nina?
Come on.
Where did you go,
why didn't you tell me?
I just asked her for work.
Okay. It's cool.
You just forgot to mention.
Hey, I'm not jealous, okay!
What?
Nothing.
You're so cute.
Yuck! What's wrong with you? Move.
Hey, by the way...
what kind of work
did Miss Nina offer?
Knock-Out.
What do you think?
Should I take it?
Up to you.
If you think you can take it.
Do you have other options?
There's your answer.
This used to be a warehouse.
Closed because of the pandemic.
You can use anything you like here.
Shower and lockers at the back.
That's Anjo. He's one
of the best boxers here.
Last night he won 250 thousand.
Talk to him, maybe he'll give you tips.
Don't be fussy.
Here, water.
Let's eat!
Kate!
- Kate, let me explain!
- Let go of me!
What's your problem?
What?
I thought you said it's cool.
You said that.
It's fine if it's with someone
you know, hell, that's even better.
I thought it was okay.
I really did.
But when I saw you
with Nina, it felt different.
This setup used to be fine
with my exes, I was okay with it.
I didn't have a problem, but,
I don't know.
I don't know anymore.
What is it?
Just wait.
I have something to confess.
I just want to know if
Jessy is the girl from the app.
And I'm telling you,
you can be part of our operation!
As an informant.
Get in, know how things work.
Use that lady friend you met.
As soon as when we have enough evidence--
if there's prostitution, or
anything illegal associated with
that online gambling,
then we'll take them to court.
Of course, you'll get a reward.
It's not much, but it'll help.
It'll help your life with
that woman you're looking for.
I said yes.
Fuck you!
Listen to me.
I'm falling for you.
Sorry I didn't tell you.
Is that from a script the
police told you to say?
I love you.
Here's your coffee.
Good morning.
Yes?
Is Kate there?
Come in.
Thanks.
Not here.
She's not here.
We don't know where she is.
She didn't come home.
Did she run away?
She left her things but
she didn't say she was leaving.
What happened?
Sorry for the trouble. Sorry.
Chief. Can we talk?
About what?
The... you know...
Okay, let's talk there.
What's up?
Chief.
I can't do what you want.
I'm going crazy.
Even Kate left me!
No one knows where she is!
She's missing?
What makes you say she left you?
She's part of a gambling circle.
Anything could have happened to her.
Like?
I really don't want to say but...
she could have been kidnapped?
Killed? Beaten up?
What's the last thing you did with her?
We fought.
I told her about the operation.
You fucking moron!
Don't you know what confidential means?
I trust Kate!
And now she's missing!
What if she ran to her bosses?
What if you're next?
And you go missing, too?
Go on, leave, we're not gonna stop you.
But I can't guarantee that
you'll be safe if something happens.
What do I need to do?
Just follow our instructions.
And I'll make sure you're safe.
Deal?
Can we talk?
Why haven't you answered my texts?
I'll fight again.
I gave your slot away.
To who?
Chikoy.
He's gonna fight Anjo.
Anjo?
What can he do against Anjo?
Anjo will slaughter him!
Take him out!
Why don't you remove him instead?
Then.
Take him out.
Any news? Did you get a fight?
They didn't give it to me,
but I have a plan.
Chief. The fight is staged.
I'll place my life on your hands.
Yeah, just calm down.
We'll take care of you.
Don't worry.
Get into the fight.
Before the three rounds are over,
we'll raid the place.
We've gotten a number
of complaints about you.
But you're a legit business, right?
You have your papers,
so we won't take a swing at you.
So what do you need from us?
Does Boss Paps know about this?
We just want to partner up with you.
Partner?
How?
We're not POGO.
You wanna keep raking in cash,
don't you? So do we.
We've thought of a market
you haven't tapped into yet.
Live shows and underground boxing.
But this isn't for your small fish.
We'll just use the app
and then we'll split the spoils.
Where would we get these boxers?
Who wants to bet on something
that's underground?
We don't need to find a fighter!
Just people who can fight
and are desperate for money.
Isn't that more exciting?
Just like the battle of YouTubers!
You can use your girls, too.
What do you mean?
They can lure in men
to join the betting app.
Hold on,
I'm a little confused.
Why do you need to do this?
We're legal! Legal!
Let's just say that we need
to make a little revenue.
It's for the politicians
running next election.
It's 2025. How time flies, right?
No. I don't agree to this, alright?
I don't want this kind of trouble.
That's the wrong answer.
We'll put you through
something much worse
if you don't agree to this.
Come on!
Want the money, or not?
Thanks for your cooperation.
You won't regret it.
Thanks for your help finding Jessy.
Hello, Nina? Good afternoon, how are you?
Yes, I have a prospect for you.
Hello, sis?
Yeah?
Yeah, I'll take care of it,
I'll send money.
100 thousand minimum.
I'll take care of it, sis,
you'll have it soon.
Okay?
Fuck, man, sorry about this,
I need this fight.
Give me the fight.
Please.
Give the fight to me.
You really took it seriously.
All right.
It's yours.
But this fight is special.
What?
What do you mean?
Win or lose...
100 thousand
is the lowest you'll get.
But...
you can get as much
as 500 thousand.
Are you going to fight again?
What's the special arrangement?
You need to lose on purpose.
What?
Why would I do that?
Okay.
I'll tell you since I trust you,
we have a bettor who's
a businessman. Very wealthy!
But...
he plans to run in the next election.
He needs funds, and he needs
to win, so he can protect us.
So the fight is staged.
Do you consent?
Am I up against Anjo?
Yes.
Is there a problem?
Goddamn you, Pip, what
did you do to my brother?
Chikoy just wanted to help
send our siblings to school!
and you almost beat him to death?
He'd be in bigger trouble
if he continued the fight.
Where did you go?
- What happened to you?
- Listen very carefully!
I don't have much time.
Kate, what do you mean?
- Why are you running out of time?
- Just listen to me, please!
- The fuck happened to you?
That policeman S.E. Publito guy--
He's a pawn and in cahoots
with that fucking Nina!
They're using you as bait, Pip!
You're bait!
- Bait? Being baited the fuck where?
- Yes!
If you lose the fight with Anjo on purpose,
that means one thing.
They'll beat the shit out of you!
They'll beat you until you're dead
or bedridden for life!
What the hell are you saying? Kate?
That's what they're paying
for in large fights.
And Anjo never plays in the small ones.
Please, if you survive this fight,
just let me know.
This is the address. Find me.
Kate, pick up.
Where are you?
Where are we meeting?
Kate? Kate?
Damn it!
Bro, good morning.
Sir, please place your stuff here.
I think that Buddhist saying got
it wrong when they said that
they should kill the illusion
of Buddha before them.
Because, I'm...
I'm willing to kill
just to keep the most
beautiful illusion I have.